A figure silhouetted against a low wide window and reflected on a glossy black floor. Water falls slowly past the window, which opens onto a large hangar.
A figure, seen from above, leads a line of white-clad soldiers carrying rifles across a lava field. A line of massive four-legged armored A.T.-A.T. walkers march across an open plain, raising clouds of red dust.
A figure wearing a black mask with silver around the eye slot stands against a red background. A black-gloved hand picks up a black lightsaber hilt off a glossy table.
Rey activates a blue lightsaber, breathing determinedly. She stands against a tall cliff face.
Text, Lucasfilm L.t.d.
Aerial view of a craggy, steep island surrounded by blue water. Rey holds a metal lightsaber hilt out. A mechanical hand takes it from her.
Luke, dressed in brown robes and heavily bearded, looks deeply at her. He holds the lightsaber hilt carefully.
Rey, wearing a hooded brown cloak, picks her way through the mist over sharp rocks. A cave. Light shines onto a central platform. Rey, her face shadowed, looks down.
She swings a lightsaber on the edge of a cliff, spinning around to hold it to the side of a volcanic tuff. Rock cracking. Luke looks down, alarmed. Tiny shards of rock float upwards from Rey's hands. She closes her eyes.
A metal hand claws out of a burning pile of wood. A cloaked figure and R2-D2 watch a building burn.
Luke turns away.
Rey, tearful, clings to a flat, wide stone.
Doors open before a figure wearing a black helmet with metallic detailing around the eye slot. Kylo Ren stands in an elevator, gazing at the helmet in his hand. The scars on his face are still healing. He punches the wall.
Explosions. Spaceships veer past each other, firing bolts of energy. Kylo Ren pilots a spaceship. His ship spirals past explosions, veering into a wide hangar.
General Leia in a command center. Quick cuts between Leia and Kylo Ren.
Blue model of a spaceship in the crosshairs on a holo screen. Kylo Ren holds his thumb just above a trigger. He swallows heavily. Leia's mouth is creased with worry. Text, This Christmas.
A disc-like spaceship, the Millennium Falcon, streaks cave formations, enemy ships hot on its tail.
Chewbacca, a huge, hairy creature, opens his mouth wide. A small, wide-eyed creature copies him.
A green laser bolt ignites a ship. Poe Dameron clutches a window.
An engine thruster. A ship shoots into space. Poe speaks before a group of rebels.
Electricity dances across her reflective mask. Captain Phasma, a shining figure in a black cape, draws her sword. Finn opens a crackling energy sword. Their weapons clash, the building around them crumbling as it burns. Ships explode. BB-8, a round robot, crackles with electricity as his head spins around.
Luke, teeth gritted. A family of crystalline foxes. A wide opening with stone above and below. Leia turns away. A figure plunges into deep water. Rey pulls herself onto wet stone and stands.
Finn leading a group of white-clad Stormtroopers. A battalion of ranked soldiers. A.T.-A.T. walkers march across a wide white plane, ships exploding above them.
Ships spiral from the sky, throwing up bright red clouds as they crash.
A wizened man reaches out. Rey screams, suspended mid-air.
Rey, lit by flames. Kylo looks back at her and reaches out a gloved hand.
Title, Star Wars. The Last Jedi.
December 15. Tickets available now. In Real D 3D and IMAX 3D. This film is not yet rated.
Subscribe.